{
    "id": "c429f1628b5247a7861b89837d707185",
    "title": "Prepositions of Time Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "75626281bee547f2ad98d15b7596f054",
            "title": "Prepositions of Time",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I will be here ........................... next week.",
                    "description": "We use 'for' to indicate duration. We use since to indicate the starting point of a situation. Until shows the ending point of a situation. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for",
                        "until"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The school reopens ........................ Monday.",
                    "description": "We use on before the days of the week. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "at",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I invite my friends to dinner .......................... Christmas eve.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "in",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They are getting married ........................ the tenth of August.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They will be here from Monday ............................ Friday.",
                    "description": "Use the pattern from...to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He hasn't worked ......................... he lost his job.",
                    "description": "Since indicates the starting point of a situation. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since",
                        "until"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The work won't be complete ........................... Friday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for",
                        "until"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "They are getting married ......................... the spring.",
                    "description": "We use 'in' before seasons. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "in",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It usually rains ....................... the month of July.",
                    "description": "We use 'in' before the names of months. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You must leave ...................... evening.",
                    "description": "By evening means in the evening or before that. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "until",
                        "by",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I waited for them ......................... evening and then I went home.",
                    "description": "Until and till mean the same. Until is more formal. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "until",
                        "till",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was absent ...................... a week.",
                    "description": "We use for to indicate duration. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for",
                        "until"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}